SQL injection matters because applications often enforce access,
process sensitive information, connect to business systems,
and create operational evidence.
Teams should evaluate this issue across user-facing features, APIs, administrative tools,
cloud services, and delivery pipelines.
Command injection matters because applications often enforce access,
process sensitive information, connect to business systems,
and create operational evidence.
Teams should evaluate this issue across user-facing features, APIs, administrative tools,
cloud services, and delivery pipelines.
NoSQL injection matters because applications often enforce access,
process sensitive information, connect to business systems,
and create operational evidence.
Teams should evaluate this issue across user-facing features, APIs, administrative tools,
cloud services, and delivery pipelines.
LDAP injection matters because applications often enforce access,
process sensitive information, connect to business systems,
and create operational evidence.
Teams should evaluate this issue across user-facing features, APIs, administrative tools,
cloud services, and delivery pipelines.
Parameterized queries Input validation Output encoding Selected ISO mappings for this
topic include 8.
28 - Secure coding; 8.
29 - Security testing in development and acceptance.